Stuck in the Suburbs is a family, comedy, music film
directed by Savage Steve Holland.
Brittany Aarons  is one of the many girls who has a crush on
popular singer and boy-toy Jordan Cahill.
However, she is bored of living a suburban existence
and seeks a little something more.
Brittany Aarons, played by Danielle Panabaker.
Natasha Kwon-Schwartz, played by Brenda Song.
Kaylee Holland, played by Amanda Shaw.
Ashley Simon, played by CiCi Hedgpeth.
Olivia Hooper, played by Jennie Garland.
Eddie, played by Ryan Belleville.
Stuck in the Suburbs is a 2004 American comedy film that
premiered as a Disney Channel Original Movie.
It was released on July 16, 2004, and stars Danielle Panabaker as
Brittany Aarons and Brenda Song as Natasha Kwon-Schwartz.
Brittany, a regular middle school student in the suburbs, accidentally
exchanges cell phones with pop singer Jordan Cahill.
This was one of the first television films by Disney to
be accompanied by its own soundtrack.
The film gathered 3.7 million viewers which made the film the most-watched
telecast in its time period in the kids 6–11 and 9–14 demographics.
The film's soundtrack entered the U.S.
Billboard 200 and peaked at #5 on the Billboard Top Kid Audio charts.
The film explores themes of pop star, female friendship,
teen movie, cell phone, best friends.
The tone is lighthearted.